hi everyone my name is Baro Ferrari and
I am the financial director at students
in support of free speech at York
University I'll keep all the intros for
tonight's short because we really don't
have any time if you're ever traveling
downtown on a Tuesday night around 7
o'clock and you pass by the Isabel
Theatre the elevator theater you'll see
hundreds of people about 500 people
lined up outside and you'll ask yourself
why are there these older people younger
people why is everyone just outside
waiting in a line and it's confusing you
think maybe there's a celebrity there
you know it turns out it's Professor
Peterson discussing the psychological
significance of the biblical stories
hundreds
hundreds and hundreds of people sold-out
crowds every single week and I often ask
myself what is it about professor
Peterson that it just attracts such a
large audience and for me personally
it's how genuine he is when he speaks
many times you'll see him get on stage
and be emotional and you don't only get
that for many speakers also the
professor's command the English language
is it's so eloquent and yet so simple to
understand which you it's really unfound
nowadays it's really amazing to have
Professor Peterson here because he was
the initial inspiration behind students
in support of free speech
[Applause]
on that note it is my pleasure to
introduce professor Jordan Peterson
[Applause]
so I'm going to talk to you a bit
briefly about why post-modernism is
wrong and I actually mean technically
wrong
apart from ethically wrong and morally
wrong and intellectually wrong and
emotionally wrong and practically wrong
but I'll give it a devil is due to begin
with because they're actually wrestling
with quite a difficult problem and the
founders of post-modernism were by no
means unintelligent individuals and they
actually put your finger on quite an
important problem and the important
problem that they put their finger on
was the fact that any set of phenomena
has a near infinite number of potential
interpretations and that actually
happens to be the case that that fact
let's say was discovered simultaneously
in a number of different disciplines one
of them most surprising it was
artificial intelligence and the
artificial intelligence people ran into
that conundrum when they learned that it
was much more difficult to make a
machine that could perceive the world
that had originally been supposed you
know we're supposed to have autonomous
robots and or and functional artificial
intelligence backed by the late 60s and
of course that didn't happen and part of
the reason for that was that the
artificial intelligence researchers when
they were starting to instantiate
perception into their machines learned
that charting your course in the world
might be a trivial problem in comparison
to determining how to perceive the world
and the reason for that is that there's
a very large number of ways to perceive
the world and the postmodernist actually
caught on to this and one of the claims
they made was that well there's a near
infinite number of ways to interpret any
given text and that actually also
happens to be the case and then they
said well since there's a near infinite
number of ways to interpret any text how
do you know that any given
interpretation should should take
precedence over any other interpretation
which is also a perfectly reasonable
issue they went off the rails very
rapidly after putting forward that set
of propositions and that's partly why
they also kept their alliance with
Marxism because the problem with
post-modernism fundamentally is that if
you
agree to the proposition that all
interpretations of all phenomena are of
equal value or lack of value then you
can't act in the world and the problem
with that is that if your human being
you have to act in the world because
otherwise you you you suffer miserably
and then you die and that seems to be
that seems to be an unacceptable outcome
for most people so the issue with
post-modernism isn't so much the
erroneous claim that there are a very
large number of interpretations for any
given phenomena including the meaning of
a text the error in post-modernism is
the failure to recognize that there are
a finite number of credible
interpretations of phenomena and also a
refusal to engage with the intellectual
problem that determining what that
finite set might actually consist of and
I'll just give you a very brief overview
of how it is that we happen to solve
this problem as human beings we do it
partly biologically because we inhabit a
biological framework that's been
developed over the course of about 3.5
million years that severely constrains
the manner in which we interpret the
world and it constrains it such that we
tend to only manifest spontaneously
manifest interpretations of the world
that don't result in undue suffering and
our demise and there's plenty of ways to
be stupid enough to perish and there's
plenty of ways to be stupid enough to
suffer without meaning but there aren't
very many ways to live properly and
carefully for a long period of time in a
manner that doesn't also simultaneously
do harm to other people and so that's
the second set of constraints is that
you have biological constraints on your
perception than they're built in as a
consequence of a Darwinian process and
the second part is that you you're
forced to interact with yourself now in
this week next week and the week after
and the month after in the year after so
you have to conduct yourself in a way
that doesn't interfere with your future
life as you're living now and
simultaneously you have to conduct
yourself in a way that makes all the
other people around you want to
cooperate with you and compete with you
and maintain the relationship with you
and do that today and next week and next
month and next year and so on into the
future so there are so all though there
are a very large number of
interpretations of the world there are
unbelievably severe constraints on the
number of functional interpretations
there are in the world and one of the
things that the
humanities was supposed to be educating
people with regards towards
understanding was what the universe of
those finite functional interpretations
might might be and that's being more or
less abandoned by the universities under
the guise of post-modernism the the fact
that the post modernists dare to be
marxist is also something that I find I
would say not so much intellectually
reprehensible as morally repugnant and
one of the things that one of the things
that the post modernists postmodern
neo-marxists continually claim is that
they have nothing but compassion for the
downtrodden and I would say that anybody
with more than a cursory knowledge of
twentieth-century history who dares to
claim simultaneously that they have
compassion for the downtrodden and that
they're Marxists are revealing either
their ignorance of history that's so
astounding that it's actually a form of
miracle or a kind of or a kind of
malevolence that's so reprehensible that
it's almost unspeakable because we
already ran the equity experiment over
the course of the 20th century and we
already know what the the Marxist
doctrines have done for oppressed people
all around the world and the answer that
mostly was imprison enslave imprison
them enslave them work them to death or
execute them and as far as I can tell
that's not precisely commensurate with
any message of compassion and so I don't
think that the postmodern neo-marxist
have a leg to stand on ethically or
intellectually or emotionally err and I
think that they should be going after as
hard as possible from an intellectual
perspective an informed intellectual
perspective and this is fundamentally a
war of ideas and that's the that's the
level of analysis that it should be
fought upon and not only is it a war of
ideas I think it's one that can be won
because I think that the especially the
French intellectual post modernists are
a pack of what would you call them well
we could start with charlatans that's
good ones so pseudo intellectual would
be good resentful would be another and
then I would also consider them highly
they're highly deceptive in their
intellectual strategies because almost
all of them were Marx's student
intellectuals and they knew by the time
the Gulag Archipelago came out and even
before that the nightmares of the Soviet
Union and Mao's China were of such
magnitude that they had completely
invalidated any claim to ethical
justification that the fundamental
Marxist doctrines had ever managed
to manage to manifest and so it's a it's
a no-go zone as far as I'm concerned
intellectually the game's over we've
already figured out that there are
finite constraints on interpretation and
we also understand why those exist and
how they evolved and from from the
perspective of political or
argumentation there's absolutely no
excuse whatsoever in the 21st century to
put forth Marxist doctrines as if
they're the the bomb that's needed by
the compassionate and by the bomb that's
administered by the compassionate to the
downtrodden sorry tried that didn't work
we got a hundred million corpses to
prove it and that's plenty for me and if
it's not enough for you well then you
should do some serious thinking either
about your historical knowledge or about
your moral character so that's the first
thing
[Applause]
[Music]
okay so the next thing is what to do
about it and I think I thought about a
lot of things about what might be done
about it apart from just talking about
it which seems to be reasonably
effective but I thought for a while that
it would be useful for the for the for
the political systems people are running
the political systems to consider doing
something like cutting the funding of
universities by 25 percent and letting
them fight over the remains and
hopefully what that would mean hopefully
that would mean that the pseudo
disciplines such as women's studies
which never had a methodology to to to
methodology that was credible to begin
with and I would put in the same
classification all the ethnic and racial
studies groups that are popping up on
campuses like mad under the guise of of
true disciplines of which they're not in
any sense of the imagination but also or
any sets of the word but also
increasingly the social sciences and the
general humanities that have been
corrupted quite terribly by the
postmodern doctrines I thought well
maybe it would be good to see if the
funding could be cut for them because
because there's no reason that the
public at large should be funding a
fifth column whose aim is to disrupt the
fundamental structures of Western
civilization with tax money that's
devoted to supporting people while
they're doing that
[Music]
you know and I'd like to think about
that it'd be nice if that was a paranoid
delusion and of course when I first
started thinking talking about this the
first thing that people thought and
quite rightly was who the hell is this
crazy professor and how many things
might there be wrong with him which is
exactly which is exactly what you should
think when someone stands up and says
hey you know this system that you guys
all think is going really well and
that's been going wrong well for decades
there's something seriously wrong about
it but you should be paying attention to
the first thing you should think of is
well what makes you think you're not
insane and because that is the right
that is the right answer under those
circumstances but it turned out at least
as far as I can tell that I'm not
actually insane and that the things that
and that the things that I were pointing
out were actually factual and what
happens in Canada at least and I would
say to some degree around the world was
that as journalists who actually happen
to be concerned about free speech
generally speaking started to look into
the claims that I was making about such
things as the legislative policies
surrounding Bill c16 they realized that
I was actually just reading what was
written on the page and understanding it
instead of trying to blow something out
of proportion which I had absolutely no
motivation whatsoever to do but then you
know I thought I thought no you can't
have political interference with the
universities because what happens is
that you know you think what happens is
that if you arm the politicians so that
they can start telling the universities
what they can and cannot teach even with
regards to funding is then that goes
seriously sideways very rapidly and you
don't end up with the result that you
wanted you end up with some other result
because you know how it is when you
allow one organization to interfere with
the autonomous function of another is
that it isn't the people that you want
to do with the regulating that end up
doing the regulating and the things that
you end up getting regulated are the
things that you want to stop so that's
not a good idea so I think I have a
better idea and I think the better idea
is that the post modernist should be
starved at their source and and I don't
use that terminology lightly I think
that what needs to happen is that
freshman and second year university
students and and students coming into
university from high school need to be
educated about the postmodern cult and
they need to be encouraged to not take
the courses to just drop the courses to
just stay the hell away from them and
the humanities enroll
have been declining precipitously since
the 1960s and a big part of that is that
you know why in the world would you go
as a half confused highschool student
into University and get whatever shreds
of of culture that you're still clinging
to to keep your poor head above water in
the sea of chaos that threatens to
surround you taken away by your
professors so you're stripped bare of
anything but some vague sense that maybe
you're a horrible racist unconsciously
in some manner that you can't detect and
then be left with nothing that that for
your for your hundred thousand dollar
investment in your bloody student loan
so people are smart enough maybe not to
continue to enroll in that sort of thing
over time and the humanities have been
being decimated since the 1960s as a
consequence but it's time for that
process to accelerate and so here's
something cool that happened this week I
think I decided a couple of weeks ago to
make a postmodern lexicon and I started
analyzing word use in I was gathering
abstracts from this Twitter site called
new real peer-review which is something
that the post modernists really hate and
because of course what new real
peer-reviewed does is take actual
published abstracts from postmodern
humanities journals which by the way
have a zero citation rate of 80% and
merely and merely republish them and the
abstracts are so reprehensible and so
incoherent and so cult-like
and ideologically addled that the people
who wrote them get irritated when other
people read them and which is which is a
good because the original the real
peer-review which was the first one was
shut down by people who are irritated
that the people who ran the Twitter site
had the unmitigated gall to actually
publicized writing that was written to
be publicized it was like the only
situation I've ever seen where authors
were actually embarrassed that someone
did what they could to publicize what
they'd written anyways new real peer
review picked up where they stopped and
has been publishing abstracts like mad
from these crazy postmodern journals
which are journals only in name and so I
started to pull out key keywords well
I'll tell you a little bit about that
game in a minute I started to pull out
keywords that were emblematic of let's
call it the postmodern cult and then I
thought I generated questionnaire that
that
parents of university students and and
late-stage high school students and
freshmen and university and maybe second
year students could use as a guideline
so they could look at the course
descriptions and check off word
frequency from the post-modern list and
decide that if the course was part of
the postmodern cult that they should
maybe just not take it but then I got a
real interesting email from a guy I will
tell you his name yet but who's a
computer programmer and he put together
an AI system to parse apart post-modern
the post modern lexicon automatically
and he set up a website now where
students can feed in course descriptions
of any sort and it will spit out whether
or not they're postmodern and he's
and so we're developing so the point is
to get the to get the program up to the
point where it can automatically
distinguish between postmodern and non
postmodern content and then students
will be able to cut and paste a course
description and paste it into the
analysis box on this website along with
the professor's name and the courses
name and the discipline and the
university and so we should be able to
produce a listing of every University in
every course that people are willing to
participate in analyzing across North
America and set up a list of courses and
professors and disciplines that should
be avoided and and so maybe we can
starve them out at their source and
that's what should happen
so it has it has to be bottom up as far
as I can tell for this to come to an end
and it should come to an end because the
post-modern neo-marxist doctrine is
nothing but a cult except that it's the
sort of cult that doesn't have enough
economic sense to run itself out of
profit so not only is it a cult it's a
failed cult and if it was so it's a cult
that has to be subsidized by the public
person in order to exist at all so
that's like that's a pretty damn
pathetic cult because normally if you're
a decent cult leader you can least
figure out a way to pick the pockets of
your of your victims in a manner that
enriches you so I can't even managed to
get that right which I think it counts
for the pronounced anti-capitalist bias
because they haven't been able to
transform their ideological doctrine
into some way of making themselves
spontaneously rich although it certainly
seems to have done a great job of
labeling students with observed levels
of student loans in the United States
it's exactly the point in their life
where they should be free to make
entrepreneurial decisions and take some
risks which is also something that I
regard is absolutely reprehensible
so universities have figured out how to
conspire in some sense to pick the
future pockets of the students that
they're purporting to to educate and
they're not educating them they're
indoctrinating them they're not teaching
them how to speak they're not teaching
them how to debate they're not teaching
them how to write they're not
introducing them to the classical wisdom
of the Western judeo-christian tradition
and that's an absolutely appalling
because that's what the bloody
institution was there for to begin with
and that's what it's supposed to be
doing
[Applause]
yeah so what else do I have to tell you
about that oh yes I just have one more
thing I guess that one of the things
that I'm quite was quite curious about
was um I'll tell you about two things
one of the things I was quite curious
about is the post-modern say neo-marxist
insistence that the only true human
motivation is power now I've been
thinking about that in a couple of ways
I think that was actually Marxist
sleight of hand at the end of the 1960's
because the original Marxist
revolutionary doctrine was that Western
society let's say capitalist society but
you can think about it more broadly as
society in general it's basically best
conceptualized as a zero-sum zero-sum
game fought to the death between the
oppressors and the oppressed and be the
proletariat and the Barozzi let's say
and you know as we as we know playing
that game in places like Soviet Union
and Mao's China didn't work out so well
for everyone so there seemed to be a
fundamental flaw in the
conceptualization although people could
always excuse that by saying well that's
not real communism which is the sort of
statement that should immediately get
you punched in the nose hard enough to
knock you out as far as I'm concerned
so because the statement like that
reveals only one thing and what it
reveals is that if you had been
fortunate enough to be in the position
of position of Joseph's tellement you
wouldn't have been quite the murderous
monster that he was because your moral
character is such so that you wouldn't
be swayed by access to that kind of
extreme power and if you're if you dare
to make that claim then there's some
things about yourself in humanity that
you should learn and you should learn
them rapidly before you pose more of a
danger to yourself and others than you
already pose so so then so part of it is
the post modernists turned the marxist
emphasis on economics into an emphasis
on power in the 1970s and I think they
did that as a form of sleight of hand
because by the late 1960s and early
1970s it was obvious even to people as
intransigent as someone as say jean-paul
Sartre which who refused to denounce the
Communist Party until that late and in
that progression of the 20th century
it became obvious even to people like
that that there was just no way that you
could maintain your intellectual and
moral credibility and remain a supporter
of standard communist doctrine and also
it seemed to be the case that strangely
enough contrary to Marx's prediction
that the working class in the West was
getting richer and richer than people
had ever got in history rather than
being increasingly downtrodden by the
brute heel of the of the corporate and
capitalist elite so it was not a
revolution that was particularly easy to
sell part of the site at hand was oh
it's not about economic power
it's about oppression and oppressed and
oppressors on a broader sense and that's
where we got the transformation into
identity politics which is just the
Marxist oppressor oppressed doctrine
under a new guise and I think it's
really tremendously reprehensible for
people to to be conducting themselves
intellectually in a manner that insists
that the most important element of any
student or any person for that matter is
whatever racial gender and sex identity
happens to be flavor of the month and I
think the problem with that
fundamentally is first of all that that
those category systems are
extraordinarily loose and they're
indefinitely multipliable you know
because to take any given individual
there's probably well it's the
postmodern problem there we go it's the
postmodern problem that there's almost
an infinite number of ways to categories
any given individuals so how the hell do
you figure out
which group they belong to and that's
actually a major problem like if you're
1/8 black what does that make you
exactly are you black are you white are
you oppressed are you oppressor are you
are you let's see one half is oppressed
as someone who's a quarter black does it
work out or is medically that way okay
I'm dead serious about this man if we're
going to play this sort of game that's
exactly the question that has to be
asked right and then how do you how do
you multiply up your oppressed
identities and then again who decides
who gets to decide exactly which
identity you should manifest and then
how do we rank order those identities
and then how do we equate between them
and what measurement techniques do we
use to determine who's who's oppressed
and who isn't and how do we assess
equality and on what dimensions are we
going to assess equality and who's going
to enforce it and who's going to make
the decisions it's like oh well we'll
figure that out as we go along it's like
yeah we certainly will and the results
won't be pretty I can tell you that
because because the problem is actually
unsolvable all it'll mean is that those
those categories will be made at the
whim of the people who are making the
categories and since as we know the only
thing they believe in power is power
that the only thing they believe in is
power is that you can be absolutely sure
that they will have absolutely no
hesitancy whatsoever to use power in the
seeking of their aims and I think the
other reason that all of the
postmodernist neo-marxist ever do is
talk about powers because they want to
justify their use of power to get
exactly what they want when they want it
there's nothing but power it's like
alright if there's nothing but power
that means we're at war over power and
that if that's the claim that you make
then you can justify the use of power
because there isn't anything else to
turn to there's no logic there's no
dialogue there's no consensus there's no
discussion between well-meaning people
there's nothing but divisions between
power groups and identity groups and and
a Hobbesian state of war between all of
us well when I won't look at people
anything at that then my proclivity as a
psychoanalyst is to think that that's
exactly what they want and to divide us
up all by race and ethnicity and sexual
identity and sexual preference and
sexual expression and gender identity
and all these multiplying forces of
group identities seems to be nothing but
an invitation to chaos and that's
exactly what I see looming and it needs
to come to a stop and it needs to come
to a stop as fast as possible and one
way of doing that is to stop the
universe
he's from continuing to indoctrinate
young people who really at least at the
beginning don't know any better into
playing these absolutely insane and I
would say bordering on murderous
intellectual games and so
[Music]
so then I'm going to set up this website
and maybe some other ones like it and
I'm going to do a series of videos for
young University students and for high
school students and I'm going to tell
them that perhaps they don't need to go
to university to be indoctrinated
perhaps they could go to university to
learn and if they want to know the
difference between an educator and
someone who's merely interested in it
dr. nation and the production of the
next generation of pathetic whining
radicals then they can use them then
they can use the website to distinguish
between people who are credible and
people who aren't and maybe we can drop
the damn enrollment in those horrible
courses by 75% over the next three years
and just stop it in its tracks
[Applause]
so anyways that's part of the plan and
and and I think it's I think it's
something that's actually implementable
these things can turn around fast and
one of the ways that they'll turn around
is that if people just stop taking the
courses and so what people need to do in
order to know that they should stop
taking the courses is to know that these
is to know what it is that these courses
are aiming at so that needs to be
explained then they need to know what
language the people who teach these
courses are using in order to fulfill
those aims then they need to know how to
identify the courses then they need to
know that it's in their best interest
both I would say spiritually and
economically to avoid those courses and
those disciplines like the plague and
then maybe we can get the disciplines
that have become entirely corrupt and
the ones that started that way to put
themselves back together before they run
themselves out of existence completely
and I might as well name a few of the
disciplines that I think are
particularly reprehensible to begin with
I'm obviously I'm painting this with a
very broad brush and I'm not making the
claim that every single person who
engages in activity within all of these
disciplines has been corrupted beyond
comprehension by the postmodernist
neo-marxist but it's close enough first
pass approximation so as I said already
Women's Studies and all the ethnic
studies and racial studies groups man
those things have to go and that faster
they go the better they should never be
put
there would have been banner head they'd
never been part of the university to
begin with as far as I can tell
sociology that's Kurupt anthropology
anthropology that's corrupt English
literature that's corrupt maybe the
worst defender of the faculties of
education and I would say look I read
the recent poll I read the recent policy
documents of the Elementary Teachers
Federation of Ontario and I can tell you
you can go read it it's right on their
website is that their plan and they just
say it I'm not making this up you don't
need any inferences there's there's
nothing implicit about it is to
reorganize the curriculums from
kindergarten to grade eight so that
children are taught to be social justice
warriors from the moment they step foot
in the public education system that's
exactly what they're doing they're
making that they're making that's just
look I mean we have social justice
tribunals in Ontario okay that's not
subtle in case you didn't notice to name
them social justice tribunals that's not
subtle and so you see the same sort of
language in the ETF Oh documents is that
social justice is the right way to go
the appropriate thing to do is to train
children to follow precisely that
pathway and the best way to do it is to
get them as young as possible it's like
and that's the faculties of Education
for you and they're not producing people
who are interested in educating children
at all and they're doing they're taking
the easy route and what they're doing is
training people who who can memorize and
then spew forth a one-dimensional view
of humanity and then have the goal the
unmitigated goal to presume that what
they should be doing with children is
indoctrinating them into that particular
line of thinking from as early an age as
possible and so faculties of Education
they need to be fixed and they need to
be fixed
[Music]
and then and this is where I'll stop one
of the most shocking things I learned
this years I didn't really know this but
I didn't learn this till I went to
Queen's University because I went to
Queen's University I was invited there
by a group of law students you know and
I was their hope hypothetically to
debate bill c16 and the students went to
all the law professors and asked them if
they would debate me and none of them
would and I thought well I thought yeah
well that's figures first of all that's
what I thought because well but but then
I thought jeez that's pretty absurd
because I'm a psychology professor no
lawyers one thing lawyers are pretty
good at is arguing if they're good
lawyers I mean that in a complementary
manner I mean that's what you learn to
do when you're a lawyer you learn to
speak you learn to formulate an argument
and you learn to form a I'm formulate an
argument on virtually any set of
principles because you know you're
acting as defense or you're acting as
prosecution and you need to be flexible
on your feet and put forward the best
possible argument given the facts at
hand and they couldn't find anybody to
debate me so Bruce party who's a
professor there had act as devil's
advocate which he did quite nicely but I
thought that was pretty pretty appalling
to say the least that they were either
so ideological II rigid that they
wouldn't confront me on my on their
bloody territory it's like if if he if a
law professor from Queens wanted to come
and debate me about psychology hey
there'd be no problem with that because
that after all is my field of expertise
and the fact that a law professor
wouldn't come forward and debate me on a
legal matter I thought was just I didn't
even know what to think about that but
one of the things I did learn and I
really learned this more is that law has
actually become corrupt as well as a
discipline and it's not so much I know a
lot of lawyers and I've worked with a
lot but most of them have been more on
the corporate business end of things and
so but all the human rights law all the
law that doesn't seem to be attached in
some sense to business concerns has also
become corrupt and social justice
oriented beyond belief and the students
at Queen's were complaining to me that
they weren't learning any law in their
courses all they were learning with
social justice propaganda so you bloody
well better watch out for that I can
tell you because the people who make
your legislation or lawyers and they're
making plenty of legislation that is not
in your best interest and even worse
than that perhaps it's not even in the
best interest of the people for whom the
legislation purports to
because the bloody legislation and the
policies are so incoherent and so badly
written like bill c16 here's one of the
things it did no one knows this and I
can't believe they haven't noticed you
know the strongest argument that gay
people have had for the last 50 years
for being included in broader society
and let's say tolerated so to speak or
welcomed for that matter is that it was
a biological phenomenon you know and I'd
say the evidence for that isn't
overwhelming but it's it's certainly
suggestive it's like Bill c16 has
eradicated that because it's predicated
on the presupposition that there's no
relationship that the relationship
between biological sex gender identity
gender expression and sexual proclivity
is independent they blew out the
structure that enabled them to make the
argument for including the ruin for
pursuing the rights to begin with and so
if I was a good hateful right-wing
radical and feeling rather anti-gay in
my orientation let's say I might say
something like oh I see it's just
something you learned is it well how
about you unlearn it and if it's just
your whim well then why should I put up
with it at all and that's actually
written into the damn legislation now so
so watch the lawyers because they're
being trained as social justice warriors
and they're producing incoherent bits of
legislation that are going to produce a
tremendous amount of problems as they
roll through the legal system so anyways
in closing the closing is
it's a war of ideas and it's an
educational problem and what we're going
to try to do is to educate students well
enough well they're making their course
decisions so that they can stop being
indoctrinated by people who should have
known better than to do that to begin
with and so that's the plan for the next
couple of years and hopefully it will be
effective so thank you very
[Applause]
[Music]